chinadivision.com 2019-07-03

# 

## Privacy Policy

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Chinadivision.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

### What personal information does Chinadivision.com gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shipping experience at [Chinadivision.com](http://www.chinadivision.com/). Here are the types of information we gather.  
• Information you give us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You provide most such information when you price, ship, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom packages have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers) listed in your address book; content of reviews and e-mails to us; personal description; and financial information, including Social Security and driver’s license numbers. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shipping for you, improving our site, and communicating with you.

• Automatic information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Chinadivision.com. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; shipping history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features such as shipping circles and top shippers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; routes you searched for; and the phone number you used to call our 888 number. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Chinadivision.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

• Behavioral “retargeting” Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, company, address, email address, or telephone number) cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information such as IP address, pages viewed, and if a conversion and other information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, for more information about behavioral advertising and how it uses your anonymous info, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org.

• E-mail communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Chinadivision.com if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please go to the My Account link in the header of any Chinadivision page and adjust your Newsletter preferences.

• Information from other sources: We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next shipment or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information; pricing criteria and pricing result information; and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit services to some customers.

## Does Chinadivision.com share the information it receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below.  
• Affiliated businesses we do not control: We work closely with our affiliated businesses. Examples of co-branded and joint offerings include carriers which handle the delivery of your packages, and brokers which provide your packages with cargo insurance. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party.

• Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

• Promotional offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of our customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please go to the My Account link in the header of any Chinadivision page and adjust your Newsletter preferences.

• Business transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that we, or substantially all of our assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

• Protection of Chinadivision.com and others: We release account and other personal information as necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

• Law Enforcement: Chinadivision’s policy is to notify members of requests for their data unless it is prohibited from doing so by statute or court order. Law enforcement officials who believe that notification would jeopardize an investigation should obtain an appropriate court order or other process that specifically precludes member notification.

• With your consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

## How secure is information about me?

We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming a shipment. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

## Which information can I access?

Chinadivision.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Chinadivision.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

## Children

If you are under 18, you may use Chinadivision.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

## Conditions of use, notices, and revisions

If you choose to visit Chinadivision.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the city of Shenzhen. If you have any concern about privacy at Chinadivision.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Terms of Use will change also. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

## Contact us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with Chinadivision.com, please contact Customer Support. Our Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Please visit this site often to keep up to date with our latest policies.
